





Overview

Passionate and dedicated professional with 2+ years building, testing, launching and maintaining full-stack web applications. I am highly motivated, focused, reliable and an organized worker that succeeds both on a team and individually. I have a strong background in OOP Principles, building APIs and database-driven web applications. I am seeking a Web Developer role where I can use my skills to contribute to different projects of the company and gain valuable experience and knowledge.

Education

2014 - 2018

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

Catanduanes State University

During my time at University, I developed a passionate interest for full-stack web development and never stopped learning since.

Skills

Web Technologies/Frameworks/Libraries Laravel, Flask, React, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, jQuery, Wordpress

Programming Langauges PHP7, Python, Javascript

Versioning and Other Tools Git, Github, Trello, Adobe Photoshop

Databases MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server

Core Competencies Software Develoment Life Cycle (SDLC), REST/CRUD Applications, MVC Architecture,

> Object-Oriented Programming Principles, API Design, Communication, Problem Solving, Project Management, Single-Page-Applications

Experience

May 2018 - Present

Full-Stack Web Developer

Provincial Capitol of Catanduanes - Philippines

- Developed a human resource management system suited to the customizations of the Provincial Capitol of Catanduanes.
- Learned Python (Flask) and Beautiful Soup to create a web scraper for a province-wide data analytics application.
- Created a small online survey web application which resembles the guessing surveys on Facebook. This was used for population data-analytics, also.
- Practiced regular computer troubleshooting and basic networking throughout the various departments of the Capitol.

Oct 2017 - May 2018

Freelance Web Developer

Freelance in Bicol, Philippines

- I created and maintained software for clients ranging from small businesses to large firms.
- Developed, designed and launched the current Catanduanes Midtown Inn website.
- Created an inventory system built with PHP for Catanduanes Emerald Hardware.

Nov 2017 - Jan 2018

Back-End Wordpress Developer Intern

AltPayNet Corp., - Makati, Philippines

I worked closely with Senior Developers using Wordpress and Woocommerce to create an integrated payment processor plugin.

Apr 2015 - May 2017

Part Time Store Cashier

Catanduanes Emerald Hardware - Philippines

- During my spare time in University, I worked as a cashier to keep myself busy.
- After a 3 months, I was given a new role of Tech. Support where I assisted in the installation of POS equipment and software.
- I maintained and troubleshooted the POS clients, and continued my cashier role.